reggaerecord.com 2012-10-15

# Help - ReggaeRecord.com / Dub Store Record Mart

|  |   
---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---  
| **♣ Customer's rights and privacy agreement**  
Please click one of the following items  
  | **> >**Encoding of personal information through SSL  
**> >**Customer's rights  
**> >**Privacy agreement  
**> >**Marking According to the Special Business Act  
  |   
******♣ Protection of personal information**  
At ReggaeRecord.com any personal information provided by our customers is encoded through SSL (Secure Socket Layer). Such information is saved only on the ReggaeRecord.com server. And whenever we refer to the information, the line is secured by SSL.  
Even if a third party attempts to access the information, we do our best to prevent such incidence by using the latest technology.  
******♣ Customer's rights**  
**♣ Privacy agreement **  
|  | ♦ | **About our privacy policy**  
---|---|---  
  |   | Any content of transaction or personal information that you provided us through ReggaeRecord.com server is used and managed only for the purpose of our business operation.   
We take particular care to protect private information at ReggaeRecord.com.  
Any personal information collected by us during business operations will not be passed to a third party without the customer's consent except in the following cases where;  
(1) The disclosure of information was requested by official organs such as ministries and agencies based on their legal authority,  
(2) We consider it necessary to disclose the information to protect the service provider's or customer's rights, benefits, dignity, trust and so on, or  
(3) It is necessary to disclose the information in order to conduct business with our group companies and consolidated companies.  
In case (3), we will demand the relevant group companies and consolidated companies manage the information appropriately.  
We have set an agreement for handling personal information, taking in consideration our customers' privacy for our service providers.  
**♣ Marking According to the Special Business Act**  
|  | Marking according to mail-order (door-to-door) business act in Japan  
---  
  
| 

**Company name**

| Dub Store Sound Inc.  
---|---  
  
**Operation director**

| Naoki Ienaga  
  
**Address**

| 7-13-5 Nishi-shinjuku, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo 160-0023 Japan  
  
**Telephone**

| 0120-975-540(Japan only) /03-3364-2180  
From outside Japan: +81-3-5389-1423  
  
**Fax**

| 03-5348-2181  
From outside Japan: +81-3-5348-2181  
  
**Required cost other than  
product cost**

| Shipping cost, bank charge (for bank transfer), payment-on-delivery charge (for payment-on-delivery)  
  
**Validity of order**

| As shown on the website  
  
**Sales quantity**

| Provided by e-mail or telephone on enquiry  
  
**Delivery period**

| Immediate shipment for in-stock products, and immediate notification of arrival for out-of-stock products  
  
**Payment method**

| Credit card, cash-on-delivery (with Sagawa Express or Yamato Transport),  
Credit/Debit-card-on-delivery (with Sagawa Express),  
Bank transfer, PayPal  
  
**Returning of product**

| Only defective or unordered products accepted.  
  
**Period in which returns  
are accepted**

| Within 7 days after receiving product  
  
**Cost of returning**

| Borne by ourselves
